# **Andrew Moses**

Trainer, Team Leader, Full Stack Developer

## RECENT PROJECTS

## **Management ERP - Github Repository**

Full-Stack enterprise resource planning application built with three other developers using Node, Express-Handlebars, and Sequelize ORM. Deployed through Heroku: https://polar-dawn-89598 herokuann.com/

## **Team Generator - Github Repository**

Command line interface application for team template generation. Created with Node, Inquirer, and Jest for testing.

# Central Management System ERP - Github Repository

Command line interface ERP application for organizational structuring. Following standard CRUD operations, this application was built with Node, MySQL, and Inquirer.

## PlanetSearch - Github Repository

A mobile-first geolocation and data-driven application which fetches weather forecasts and astronomical data multiple third party API's (Google Maps, Weatherstack, Le-systeme-solaire), for users interested in the outdoors and astronomy. Deployed through GitHub

pages: https://jdilla1212.github.io/Flying-Project/

Full Stack Web Developer and experienced Team Lead with a demonstrated history of success in leadership within the financial services and healthcare industries, with a continuous drive to learn, take on challenges, and refine my skills.

## **CONTACT**

Phone: (480) 612-5250

Email: andrewmosesdrive@gmail.com

Github: www.github.com/andrewmosesdrive Portfolio: www.andrewmosesdev.herokuapp.com

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## DevCore/Quicken Loans

2019 to Present

Team Leader, Trainer

Leads new team members through intensive training on all areas of knowledge related to their future careers. Mentors and coaches new trainers as they develop their skills.

## **Donor Network of Arizona**

2011 to 2019

Lead Recovery Coordinator

Directed a team of 3-5 individuals efficiently in highly adaptive and challenging situations with heavy time restrictions. Trained new and existing staff in all clinical positions, medical record and suitability review via EMR, and national certification.

#### **SKILLSETS**

## Technical:

- Visual Studio, Git, Slack, Chrome DevTools
- JavaScript, Node, Express, HTML5, CSS3, Handlebars
- MySQL, Sequelize, MongoDB, Mongoose, JawsDB
- GraphQL, jQuery, Lodash, Materialize, Bootstrap
- Unit Testing, Agile Methodology, CRUD

### **Core Competencies**

- Problem Solving
- Planning/Operations
- Research

## **EDUCATION**

# **University of Arizona**

2020

Full-Stack Web Development Certificate

# **Scottsdale Community College**

2016-2018

**Associates Degree**